Limor Ofri

Front-end web developer

054-2335130

ofrilim@gmail.com

my portfolio

in <u>limor-ofri</u>

<u>ofrilim</u>

A recent bootcamp graduate looking for a front-end web developer position. After many years in the cosmetics industry, I made a career-changing move and learned to code. I am a quick learner, passionate about coding and building beautiful applications. In my free time I volunteer at the She Codes organization, working on expanding my knowledge of web technologies. I will begin my studies towards Computer Science B.Sc at The Open University next semester.

Education

9/2019 - 1/2020 Web Development Bootcamp at Coding Academy.

Intensive coding course (~600 hours) that covers all fundamentals of web development. During this course, I gained experience building various front-end and back-end projects from scratch (see GitHub).

Professional Experience

1/2020 - Present Instructor at She Codes, Tel Aviv University branch, volunteer.

In charge of front-end development courses. In-person teaching and

tutoring women through their first steps in coding.

1/2019 - 9/2019 Office manager at TipRanks.

Performed administrative and HR duties.

2006 - 2019 Self employed in the field of Cosmetics.

Over the span of 14 years I owned a private business providing different kinds of beauty treatments. As a business owner, my responsibilities included but were not limited to PR, accounting, administrative work, customer relations,

and logistics.

Tech Skills

- JavaScript (ES6), HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap
- Ajax, Axios
- Vue.js, React.js, jQuery
- Node.js, Express.js
- REST APIs, Web sockets
- MongoDB
- Git, GitHub, Visual Studio Code

Military Service

2002 - 2004 Completed the mandatory service as a squad commander training

new recruits.

Languages

- Hebrew Native
- English Fluent